[music]
>> All right, how's it going?
Oh, really I think the story yesterday
was man we had three series in the third
quarter defensively and offensively.
That's really what bit us. Uh
you know, we uh
basically three touchdowns in 12 plays
on defense and then we have nine plays
uh for 6 yards uh total.
You know, really in that kind of third
quarter stretch. So man that that uh
that was tough. You know, there was a
number of errors that we had uh
you know, some technique fundamental
things that we got to get cleaned up
that you can't get away with with a team
like that. Um that really got us. You
know, you you do anything
on any one of those series offense or
defense and it and it change the dynamic
of that game. So that was not good. Uh
that's what bit us.
Um
and so you know, there again man we
clean it up. We move on. So I know this
uh
you know, we got the right guys. We're
resilient team and uh we got to win. We
got to win. We got Pittsburgh at home.
So we're going to get prepared for them.
We know they're a physical team. They're
well coached.
Uh they're in the hunt over there. And
so
um we still got an opportunity. So we
got to make the most of it.
Questions?
You talked about it uh last night just
now that you got to look at the the the
performance defensively. What maybe
jumped out at as why you guys weren't
able to to limit them in really both
phases defensively?
>> Well, look I I think some of you know,
we we said going into that game really
on both sides of the ball it was ground
supremacy. We did not own the ground.
You know, and that makes it extremely
difficult uh defensively to defend those
guys if you cannot even corral or limit
their run game. Um so it started there.
They did a number of things
uh in the runs, you know, the turbo
motions, the inserts with the tight
ends. They force your corners to be
support on the inside. Just a couple of
tricky things and then that happens. Now
your outside backer has to be the one
who sets that. Just all these little
things that we we got to be much crisper
on. We're going to get it from
Pittsburgh.
That's what they do. Um
so they got us a little bit and then
just you know, using our help in some
areas on the back end. You know, we know
that uh
that Puka's a hell of a player.
Um
you know, Stafford, you know, uh played
an outstanding game for them. Uh
you know, was on really that whole game
and uh and that 12 minute ton of plays
and
and uh
you know, we we tried to limit
you know, we tried to limit some of his
production. We just couldn't quite get
there and and some of look man we got to
use our help a little better in areas.
You know, so
so I think that's a big thing is man
know where your help is. Make sure you
use your help. You know, don't go don't
go out on your own and you know, try to
make it mano e mano. Use it. Um
And so that's some of it and then you
know, like I said offensively we just we
got to get our run game going. You know,
we got to find a run game here and
reduce the stress
you know, in some of the pass game uh
protection stuff.
Yeah, we talked to you about the
win-loss win-loss narrative of you guys
always bouncing back and no no no
back-to-back losses in years now.
But when it basically comes down to you
guys need a winning streak to get in the
playoffs, what's the message to your
guys going to be this week? It'll be the
same thing. You know, we nothing can you
can't have a streak without winning the
first one. So you know, all our focus
has got to be on Pittsburgh and uh
you know, and and everything we've got
man and digesting this game plan.
Understand this opponent you're getting
ready to face. You need to know exactly
who who probably most of your
one-on-ones are going to be against, the
way they play, the style of play.
Um we got to play freaking disciplined
football. We did a good job protecting
the football. We got to take away. Well,
we we got to continue to protect it and
we need more than one. We need more than
one takeaway, you know. I thought we had
a number of guys go after the football.
You know, Jack Campbell he really got
another two out. Um we just didn't come
up with them, but that's got to stay uh
that's got to stay that way. But listen
you it's frustrating, but you can't go
down in the dumps and we can't feel
sorry for ourselves and and I don't
think we will. I really don't. We don't
have those type of guys. We go back to
work. And so you want a streak, you win
the first one. Then you worry about the
next one after that.
What about Navion?
Uh
He had a hand injury, you know, uh we'll
see where it's at. I I'm hopeful that
he'll be able to go. I'm hopeful, but
there again I we'll know more probably
in the next couple of days. Is he having
an MRI done or what?
Yeah, he had an MRI. Yep.
>> [clears throat]
>> Uh yeah, a hand injury. So it it's you
know, it's something that it could
affect him a little bit. Uh
but I think we'd like to believe he he's
going to have a chance to play here, but
until we get through practice um we
won't entirely know.
Speaking of the corner room, you guys
ask a lot of those boundary corners. Um
it's been a tough few weeks for those
guys. Is there anything you guys can be
doing to maybe loosen the load, make
their job a little bit easier? Yeah,
there there are some things we can do to
help and we tried to get to some of that
later in the game.
Um
and
and uh yeah, there there are some things
we can do and there again
you know, there's some give and take
with that. You know, wherever you try to
reduce stress now you're putting it on
somewhere else. Um you know, and and we
tried to get to where some of it was
stopping the run in a lighter box um
to try to help a little bit. And so so
absolutely there's some things we can
help you know, we can help with. We were
just talking about it upstairs. Shep
made a couple of comments, you know, as
we were watching it and
and uh
you know, and that's really what you're
trying to do is man how how can you
how how can you relieve a little bit of
stress off one area and put it on
another group and just spread the load.
You know, really you want to do that on
all sides if you can.
And
DJ Reed was playing so well before his
injury, the Baltimore game, the
Cleveland game. Feels like he's trying
to find that flow still since coming
back. Just I guess what have you made of
his play since coming back off of the
injury? Well, there again those guys man
they're put out on an island, you know,
and I know everybody knows that. They're
like quarterbacks man. You you get out
there and and there's nowhere to run,
nowhere to hide. And so
um
you know, you're not going to win all
those battles. Um
and you know, sometime sometimes things
don't go your way and you may have a
little bit of a stretch, but
I mean we I know him well enough to know
that whatever it is he he's going to
continue to work himself through it.
He's going to come out of this and he's
going to be just fine. So um you know, I
mean he went after it last week. He
continued to work. Um
and he's going to be all right. He'll be
all right. And with the with the um the
last three games coming up, you know,
you talked week to week about needing to
clean things up. Just with kind of like
time running out, what's the concern
level about being able to get those
things cleaned up with enough time as
you're trying to make this playoff push?
>> Yeah, well there again you just man you
go through the study. I know this, you
know, you you say it a number of times.
You got to say it a different way. You
know, you got to show it a different
way.
Um and so
you never know
the way that you say it may be the
difference this time or or how it how
you get that point across. And so you
just man you you keep changing it up.
You keep you keep trying to address
things in a different way.
Um
and and I do believe we'll get it
cleaned up. You know, I do believe we'll
correct those errors. And then it's on
some of these other guys just cuz it
didn't happen to you. You you've got to
learn from that rep too. You know,
that's across the board.
Um
you know, we look we got some guys that
are that are in there that have been
role players that that have an
opportunity that
they're getting uh significant reps
right now, but they got to grow from
them. They got to learn from them.
Um
so
you know,
the only way I know is to go back to
work and you put together a good game
plan. You have good practices. You have
good meetings.
And uh and then you go execute, you
know, you you turn it over and let those
guys go cut it loose. And we got to do
that this week. Have you Have you been
in a position like this as a player
where you've had your back against the
wall and like can kind of like to share
a message with them of how to get over
this? Dude, go to work, man. Go back to
work.
Go back to work. That's the message and
don't worry about the what ifs this.
Yeah, we got to win. So be it. We wanted
to win week one. We wanted to win week
two. We want to win week eight. We want
We want to win this one. So
keep putting the work in, the focus, the
detail and
and trust the guy next to you is going
to do his job. You do your job. Do it
the very best you can do do it and uh
and let's go find a way to win a game.
During that nine play stretch, offensive
stretch that started the the second
half, is there anything you would have
done differently?
It's so tough because you know, I wanted
to get the run game going, you know, and
uh
and you run, you get a solid run and
then we run it again and then we get the
holding penalty, you know, and so then
you're trying to overcome that. Try to
run again. Run it three plays in a row.
Probably should have thrown it, you
know.
Um then we come back. We go for a shot
and we just barely miss on that with you
know, JG and uh
and uh and Jamo man that was that was
about to be huge, man. Had it in his
hands and you know, hits the ground.
Just couldn't quite come up with it,
man. It was a
we were so close. That would have been a
significant play, but now we're second
and 10, you know, and then we get a sack
and now you're third and 22. So it just
uh it was tough. Come back to third
series try to get the run game going 2
yards, you know, so we just we could not
uh we could not execute in that kind of
nine play stretch and it was really the
you know, uh we were not able to
overcome the the play the negative plays
really the penalty and then you know, we
don't we don't make that play
um
on the first down and and now you're
kind of behind the sticks, but that's
what we're charged with. We got to be
able to overcome it. So,
it's hard to say. Hindsight, it's always
like, well, I should have done this and
so that didn't work, but I don't
necessarily
um regret it, I guess, cuz I did want to
get the running game going.
Dan, real fast, did you seek any further
clarification on the touchdown to
Parkinson?
No, I mean, we're going to ask about it,
you know, um but no, they they were just
hey, this is uh
so, you know, it's like I said last
night, the call stands. That was as good
as I got.
>> [music]
[music]